<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

	<WVC_TrueXenotypesSettings>True Xenotypes</WVC_TrueXenotypesSettings>

	<WVC_TrueXenotypes_Tab_XenotypesSettings>Xenotypes</WVC_TrueXenotypes_Tab_XenotypesSettings>

	<WVC_Label_enable_TrueParentGenes>True parent genes</WVC_Label_enable_TrueParentGenes>
	<WVC_ToolTip_enable_TrueParentGenes>If enabled, it adjusts the gene set in children, they receive all the parents' genes, including archite genes if both parents have them. Affects pregnancy only.</WVC_ToolTip_enable_TrueParentGenes>

	<WVC_Label_enable_TrueXenotypes>True xenotypes</WVC_Label_enable_TrueXenotypes>
	<WVC_ToolTip_enable_TrueXenotypes>If enabled, it adjusts the pawn's xenotype after gene implantation. The xenotype is assigned relative to the greatest match. Works only if the pawn xenotype remains a baseliner after implantation. Also works for newborns. 

Minimum match must be 75%, otherwise the name and icon are randomized, but the xenotype remains a baseliner.</WVC_ToolTip_enable_TrueXenotypes>

	<WVC_XaG_CustomXenotypesImport_Label>(DEV) Custom xenotypes converter</WVC_XaG_CustomXenotypesImport_Label>
	<WVC_XaG_CustomXenotypesImport_Desc>All custom xenotypes can be converted into standard xenotypes. Xenotypes converted in this way inherit: the name, genes and inheritance of the selected xenotype. Converted xenotypes are created when the game starts.</WVC_XaG_CustomXenotypesImport_Desc>

	<WVC_XaG_DialogCustomXenotypesImport>Convert</WVC_XaG_DialogCustomXenotypesImport>
	<WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport>Convert custom xenotypes</WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport>
	<WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport_Reset>Remove custom xenotype from convert list</WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport_Reset>
	<WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport_Reseted>Сonverted xenotype were removed.</WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport_Reseted>
	<WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport_ResetWarning>The removed xenotype cannot be returned. Are you sure?</WVC_XaG_ButtonCustomXenotypesImport_ResetWarning>

	<WVC_XaG_DialogCustomXenotypesImport_Success>The xenotype has been converted and will be loaded the next time you start the game.</WVC_XaG_DialogCustomXenotypesImport_Success>

	<WVC_Label_enable_CustomXenotypeImporter>Enable custom xenotype convert</WVC_Label_enable_CustomXenotypeImporter>
	<WVC_ToolTip_enable_CustomXenotypeImporter>If enabled, the necessary defs will be created for converted xenotypes when the game starts.</WVC_ToolTip_enable_CustomXenotypeImporter>

	<WVC_Label_enable_GenesGroups>Enable genes group (Prototype)</WVC_Label_enable_GenesGroups>
	<WVC_ToolTip_enable_GenesGroups>If enabled, allows you to replace gene defs that are marked as "identical".

How it works. After enabling, 2 tabs appear:
  - Genes - it contains all genes, you can create a gene group there and add any genes you want.
  - Genes group - Contains all gene groups, and allows you to delete the contents of groups.

Gene groups are lists, where there is a Main gene and all the others. When the game creates a gene, these lists are requested and if the gene being created is on the list, it is replaced with the Main gene from the group.

This option does not delete gene defs, in the editor, in descriptions and in everything else, old genes will be mentioned, but when created, they will be replaced with others. This means that hardcoded defs will remain tied to old genes and the triggers that they pull will not work.

!!! This option is a prototype, and may not be supported in the future or will be reworked, keep this in mind. !!!</WVC_ToolTip_enable_GenesGroups>

	<WVC_TrueXenotypes_Tab_GenesSettings>Genes</WVC_TrueXenotypes_Tab_GenesSettings>
	<WVC_TrueXenotypes_Tab_GenesGroupSettings>Genes groups</WVC_TrueXenotypes_Tab_GenesGroupSettings>
	<WVC_TX_GeneGroup_Search>Search</WVC_TX_GeneGroup_Search>
	<WVC_TX_ResetGeneGroup>Reset</WVC_TX_ResetGeneGroup>
	<WVC_TX_AddGeneToGeneGroup>Add gene to group</WVC_TX_AddGeneToGeneGroup>
	<WVC_TX_RemoveGeneFromGroup>Remove gene from group</WVC_TX_RemoveGeneFromGroup>
	<WVC_TX_GeneRemoveSucces>Gene removed from group.</WVC_TX_GeneRemoveSucces>
	<WVC_TX_CreateGeneGroup>Create group from gene</WVC_TX_CreateGeneGroup>
	<WVC_TX_GeneGroupCreateSucces>Group created.</WVC_TX_GeneGroupCreateSucces>
	<WVC_TX_GeneGroupAddToGroupSucces>Gene added to group.</WVC_TX_GeneGroupAddToGroupSucces>
	<WVC_TX_RemoveGroup>Remove this group</WVC_TX_RemoveGroup>
	<WVC_TX_Title>Group similar genes</WVC_TX_Title>

</LanguageData>